(Wil:)Well, not everybody felt that way.
(Wil:)A lot of people
really hated the character,
(Wil:)and some of them
hated me because of it.
(Wil:)I would do interviews,
(Wil:)and people would be mean to me.
(Sheldon:)That just happened to me.
(Sheldon:)Next time you're stuck for a tweet,
(Sheldon:)feel free to say
what a jerk Ira Flatow is.
(Amy:)Sheldon, the point is
Wil learned to embrace
(Amy:)that part of his life and
moved on to bigger and better things.
(Wil:)Yeah, I'm an author now,
(Wil:)I do public speaking,
(Wil:)and I have my own web series
about board games.
(Amy:)We're trying to cheer him up, so...
(Wil:)I'm just saying
that there was a time
(Wil:)when I thought I would never get
out of Wesley Crusher's shadow.
(Wil:)But now, it's just one small part
of a pretty great life,
(Wil:)and it's a part
that I'm happy is there.
(Sheldon:)I do see what you're saying.
(Sheldon:)That helps.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Would you two like to stay
and play trains with ms?
(Ira:)-Sure.
-Okay.
Oh, great!
(Sheldon:)Now... I work the controls.